<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dr. Tobias R. Mayer</title>
    <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dr. Tobias R. Mayer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://tobiasrm.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tobiasrm.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Currently I am currently working as a Senior IT Security Engineer at ConnectedCare GmbH (Berlin/Telgte, Germany, formerly Bewatec GmbH), where I significantly contribute to the IT security of the ConnectedCare platform and serve as the contact person for all topics related to IT security &amp;amp; data protection.
My activities address two important areas: a) technical security and b) regulatory activities. Both areas interact closely (e.g. fulfilling vulnerability management for the Cyber Resilience Act or risk management for NIS-2) and must always be planned together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expertise</title>
      <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/expertise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tobiasrm.github.io/expertise/</guid>
      <description>Certifications EC-Council  &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  Ethical Hacker &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  Encryption Specialist &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  SOC Analyst Other  Datenschutzbeauftrager (TÜV) gemäß DSGVO und BDSG-neu (TUEV-NORD) [Certificate]
Professional training as data protection officer according to GDPR and the &amp;lsquo;BDSG-neu&amp;rsquo; (a German national law for data protection), more info see course description (German-only)  Professional Experience My experience encompasses many years of work as an IT Security Professional in the corporate sector, as well as applied research at national (DE / FR) and international (IARC/WHO) institutes, typically trilingual (EN / FR / DE) and in an international / multicultural context:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tobiasrm.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Anonymous voting using distributed ledger-assisted secure multi-party computation, M. Schiedermeier, O. Hasan, T. Mayer, L. Brunie, H. Kosch. In: Applied Network Sciences Vol. 9, Springer Nature, 2024. [link] A transparent referendum protocol with immutable proceedings and veriﬁable outcome for trustless networks, M. Schiedermeier, O. Hasan, T.R. Mayer, L.- Brunie, H. Kosch. In: Proceedings of the 8th International Conference on Complex Networks and Their Applications, Springer International Publishing, 2019, 647—658. [link]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tobiasrm.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You want to contact me? That&amp;rsquo;s great! Write me an email and I come back to you as soon as possible.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
