<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dr. Tobias R. Mayer</title>
    <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dr. Tobias R. Mayer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://tobiasrm.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tobiasrm.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Specialist in Distributed Secure Systems  Currently I&amp;rsquo;m currently working as Snr. IT Security Engineer at BEWATEC ConnectedCare and contribute significantly to the IT security of the ConnectedCare platform. I am the contact person for all IT security issues and bring security &amp;amp; data protection into the company and to the patients.
Before I was involved as IT Security Analyst at Verimi in the areas of security, risk &amp;amp; workflow analysis as well as technology &amp;amp; architecture security (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expertise</title>
      <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/expertise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tobiasrm.github.io/expertise/</guid>
      <description>Certifications EC-Council  &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  Ethical Hacker &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  Encryption Specialist &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  SOC Analyst Other  Datenschutzbeauftrager (TÜV) gemäß DSGVO und BDSG-neu (TUEV-NORD) [Certificate]  &amp;ndash; more info see course description (German-only)  Professional Experience With specialization in secure distributed systemsI gained experiences coordination, analysis, research &amp;amp; development activities in French, German and international institutes, all being international &amp;amp; multicultural environments:
 Seit 07/2020: Senior IT Security Engineer BEWATEC ConnectedCare, Berlin, Germany Overall planning and implementation of IT security, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tobiasrm.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>A transparent referendum protocol with immutable proceedings and veriﬁable outcome for trustless networks, M. Schiedermeier, O. Hasan, T.R. Mayer, L.- Brunie, H. Kosch. In: Proceedings of the 8th International Conference on Complex Networks and Their Applications, Springer International Publishing, 2019, 647—658. [link]
See also pre-publication at arXiv: [arXiv:1909.06462] Deliverable D2.2: Incremental report on provenance, trust and reputation models – Technical Realization (network &amp; storage layer), T. R. Mayer. Project Report (WP1 Value Assessment), Project “Linked Data for Prescriptive Analytics: Application to Fraud Detection, Value Assessment” with Atos/Worldline industrial partner, 03/2018 (confidential, not publicly accessible).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://tobiasrm.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tobiasrm.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You want to contact me? That&amp;rsquo;s great! Write me an email and I come back to you as soon as possible.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
